Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 237 records 1968-2002 IBT0041
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local 237 records
1968-2012
1995-2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0041
1.75 Linear Feet
This collection contains material from IBT Local 237 of New York, NY dating from 1968-2012. The bulk of the materials date from 1995-2012, and include newsletters, flyers, news clippings, photographs and oral histories.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2012 [2012.081].
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material from IBT Local 237 of New York, NY dating from 1968-2012. The bulk of the materials date from 1995-2012, and include newsletters, flyers, news clippings, photographs and oral histories.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor and laboring classes; Labor unions; Labor; Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York -- History -- 20th century
- Events, 1994-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Flyers, 2008-2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Letter, Mrs. Martin Luther King, Jr. to Public Services Employee Union, 1968 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Local 237 News and Views, 1994 March - 1995 May (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Local 237 Newsline, 1995 June - December (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Local 237 Newsline, 1996 January - July (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Local 237 Newsline, 1996 August - 1997 April (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Local 237 Newsline, 1997 May - November (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2003 January - August (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2003 September - 2004 April (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2004 May - December (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Local 237 Newsline, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Local 237 Oral History Project, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- News Clippings, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Retiree Division Anniversary Commemorative Journals, 2000-2010 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Retiree News and Views, 2011 September - 2012 August (Box 4, Folder 4)